Muse (Mu-Tsz) Chen

mutsz@umich.edu | 734-730-1184 https://www.linkedin.com/in/mutsz

UX, UI Designer / Product Designer

Portfolio: mutsz.com

Summary

A UX Designer with 3 years experience. Looking for a fulltime position starting from May, 2017.

Skills

UX Methods

Contextual Inquiry Competitive Analysis Rapid Prototyping Persona Building **Usability Testing** Storyboard Heuristic Evaluation Wireframes & Mockups Affinity Wall Interview Survey

Design

Photoshop Illustrator After Effects Sketch

Photography InVision / Marvel OmniGraffle

Front-End Development

HTML / CSS **JavaScript JQuery** D3.js Python

Experience

UX/UI Designer Intern

@DNAnexus, Mountain View

May 2016 - Aug. 2016

- Designed dashboard for DNAnexus web platform, conducted user interview sessions, iterated 10 versions of prototype, define interaction patterns and finalize hi-fi designs.
- · Defined a style guide to enhance visual consistency of web application interface in DNAnexus product.

Interaction Designer @Ad2iction Interaction, Taipei

Mar. 2015 - Jun. 2015

- Designed interaction flows and interaction patterns, and animated those with HTML5, JavaSciprt, Adobe Edge and After Effects in mobile application.
- Defined information architecture, built prototypes, and consulted clients with solutions for revision of their UI and products.

Web Designer @Taipei Digital Group, Taipei

Nov. 2012 - Jul. 2014

- · Designed 7 websites for companies, consulted with clients about product problems and goals, defined visual language for web interfaces, and iterated prototypes.
- Cooperated with front-end and back-end engineers to implement design. Realized CSS3 micro-interaction animation with After Effects and Javascript.
- Successfully introduced and implemented Web Responsive Design method in business.

User Experience Design Intern

@Isobar, Taipei

Aug. 2010 - Jan. 2011

- Created ideas for brands and products with creative teams for mobile app, websites and augmented reality activities.
- · Clients including 7-11, Adidas and Testrite Group.

Education

University of Michigan, School of Information (GPA 3.93)

M.S. in Human Computer Interaction | Ann Arbor, Michigan | Present to Apr. 2017

Tsing-Hua University (Exchange Student)

Major in Art and Design | Beijing, China | Aug. 2013

National Taiwan University (GPA 3.95)

Major in Drama and Theater | Taipei, Taiwan | Aug. 2012

Minor in Psychology

Honors

Top 12 Papers in AMC, CHI conference

- · CHI Student Design Competition, 2016
- 62 submissions
- Research Publication archived in AMC Digital Library

App winner in iOSDevCamp

- · 3 Days iOSDevCamp Hackathon at PayPal
- · 31 teams